Blair and Lee Family Papers, 1640-1946 (bulk 1812-1920 ): Finding Aid C0614
Manuscripts Division
- Papers of Blair Lee, 1740-1946; 1857-1925; 218 boxes (1 partial)
  - Correspondence, 1740-1930; 84 boxes
    - General: A-Z, 1866-1930; 16 boxes 4 folders
      - Washington Railway and Electric Company, 1902-1911; 1 folder (Box 333, Folder 6)
      - Washington Regatta - Washington Times Co., 1889-1909; 1 folder (Box 333, Folder 7)
      - Washington, Woodside and Forest Glen Railway and Power Company regarding Grace Church (some documents included), 1901-1910; 1 folder (Box 333, Folder 8)
      - Wasserbach - Wetmore, 1890-1912; 1 folder (Box 333, Folder 9)
      - Wharton - Whitney, 1890-1917; 1 folder (Box 333, Folder 10)
      - Who's Who - Williams, 1879-1918; 1 folder (Box 333, Folder 11)
      - Wilmer, Re Lewis, 1908; 1 folder (Box 333, Folder 12)
      - Wilmer, Wm. Holland, 1894-1908; 1 folder (Box 333, Folder 13)
      - Wilson - Woodside School, 1887-1911; 1 folder (Box 334, Folder 1)
      - Woodward - Wright, 1890-1918; 1 folder (Box 334, Folder 2)
      - X - Y - Z (general), 1892-1918; 1 folder (Box 334, Folder 3)
      - Unidentified, 1896-1918; 1 folder (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Bound Correspondence, 1882-1887; 1 folder (Box 334, Folder 5)
      Contains miscellaneous personal, family, political, legal, and business letters during the years 1882-1887.
    - Invitations, 1863-1887; 3 folders (Box 335, Folder 1-3)
    - Calling Cards, 1876-1896; 4 folders (Box 335, Folder 4-7)
    - Address Books, 1881; 1 box
      - Address Book, 1881; 1 folder (Box 336, Folder 1)
      - Political, undated; 1 folder (Box 336, Folder 2)
      - Address book, undated; 1 folder (Box 336, Folder 3)
  - Legal Files, 1830-1935; 43 boxes (1 partial)
    Consists of correspondence, documents, notes, miscellaneous material, and printed matter pertaining to individual cases in which Lee represented one of the parties.
    - Cases, 1857-1935; 39 boxes
      Contains correspondence, documents, notes, miscellaneous material, and printed matter pertaining to individual cases in which Lee represented one of the parties.
      - Armstrong v. Ashley et al., 1893-1906; 2 folders
        - Correspondence, etc., 1893-1902; 1 folder (Box 337, Folder 1)
        - Printed Matter, 1903-1906; 1 folder (Box 337, Folder 2)
      - Baltimore Card Co., 1884; 1 folder (Box 337, Folder 3)
      - Beck, James (1822-1890) regarding his estate, 1857-1920; 1 box 3 folders
        - Documents, 1890-1899; 1 folder (Box 337, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence, 1859-1920; 6 folders
          - A - J (general), 1882-1915; 1 folder (Box 337, Folder 5)
          - L - W (general), 1859-1920; 1 folder (Box 337, Folder 6)
          - George Beck, 1889-1899; 1 folder (Box 338, Folder 1)
          - James Beck - estate correspondence prior to his death, 1877-1890; 1 folder (Box 338, Folder 2)
          - Bettie Beck Goodloe, 1890-1899; 1 folder (Box 338, Folder 3)
          - Aaron Maltby, 1881-1892; 1 folder (Box 338, Folder 4)
        - Printed Matter, 1857-1893; 1 folder (Box 338, Folder 5)
        - Receipts and Miscellaneous Material, 1876-1903; 1 folder (Box 338, Folder 6)
      - Belknap, William W: estate, 1884-1892; 1 folder (Box 339, Folder 1)
      - Bowman, Lucinda Ann: estate, 1893-1903; 1 folder (Box 339, Folder 2)
      - Brandenburg v. Dewey, 1897-1919; 1 folder (Box 339, Folder 3)
      - Brashears, Sarah Ellen: will, 1893-1909; 1 folder (Box 339, Folder 4)
      - Documents, 1886-1900; 1 folder (Box 339, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, etc., 1886-1904; 1 folder (Box 339, Folder 6)
      - Brown and Munsell Gun case, 1889-1918; 3 boxes
        - Documents, 1889-1914; 3 folders (Box 340, Folder 1-3)
        - Correspondence, 1898-1918; 1 box 2 folders
          - James Armstrong, 1905-1909; 1 folder (Box 340, Folder 4)
          - D. Owen Brooke, 1903-1913; 1 folder (Box 340, Folder 5)
          - "The Brown Segmental Wire-tube Gun", 1898-1913; 1 folder (Box 341, Folder 1)
          - Diamond Drill & Machine Co., 1899-1905; 1 folder (Box 341, Folder 2)
          - E. & G. Brooke Iron Co., 1899-1903; 1 folder (Box 341, Folder 3)
          - E. & G. Brooke Iron Co., 1903-1910; 1 folder (Box 341, Folder 4)
          - S. B. Elkins, 1904-1906; 1 folder (Box 341, Folder 5)
          - King & King, 1904-1913; 1 folder (Box 341, Folder 6)
          - Miscellaneous (A - Z), 1898-1918; 1 folder (Box 341, Folder 7)
          - Sumner B. Stiles, 1903-1906; 1 folder (Box 341, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous Material, 1898-1915; 1 folder (Box 342, Folder 9)
          Includes blueprints.
        - Printed Matter, 1889-1917; 4 folders
          - Court Records, 1898-1909; 2 folders (Box 342, Folder 10-11)
          - Miscellaneous, 1889-1917; 1 folder (Box 342, Folder 12)
          - Proofs, undated; 1 folder (Box 342, Folder 13)
      - Brown v. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Co, 1887-1894; 2 folders
        - Documents, Correspondence, etc., 1887-1894; 1 folder (Box 343, Folder 1)
        - Testimony, undated; 1 folder (Box 343, Folder 2)
      - Buckingham, Benjamin: Estate, 1906-1907; portions of 2 folders (Box 343, Folder 4)
        - Estate Documents, 1906-1907; 1 folder (Box 343, Folder 3)
        - Estate Correspondence, 1906-1907; 1 folder (partial) (Box 343, Folder 4)
      - Bryson, Andrew: Estate, 1892; 1 folder (Box 344, Folder 1)
      - Byrnes v. Baker, Mullican, Lazenby, etc, 1872-1913; 5 folders
        - Documents, 1876-1907; 2 folders (Box 344, Folder 2-3)
        - Correspondence, 1872-1913; 2 folders (Box 344, Folder 4-5)
        - Receipts, Checks, etc., 1876-1907; 1 folder (Box 344, Folder 6)
      - Carpenter, Annie, 1886-1907; 2 folders
        - Estate Documents, 1886-1903; 1 folder (Box 345, Folder 1)
        - Estate Correspondence, 1895-1907; 1 folder (Box 345, Folder 2)
      - Carroll, S. S., General: Regarding Estate, 1872-1897; 2 folders (Box 345, Folder 3-4)
      - Cole, Thaddeus P.: Bankruptcy, 1888-1896; 1 folder (Box 345, Folder 5)
      - Connell v. Reidy, 1883-1892; 1 folder (Box 346, Folder 1)
      - Cook v. Cook, 1904-1905; 1 folder (Box 346, Folder 2)
      - Craiger, S. M., 1900-1912; 1 folder (Box 346, Folder 3)
      - Cropper, John: estate, 1905-1915; 1 folder (Box 346, Folder 4)
      - Crozier, Susan E.: estate, 1902-1910; 1 folder (Box 346, Folder 5)
      - Davis, Barnes, Maris trust estate, 1881-1910; 2 boxes
        - Documents, 1881-1903; 1 box (Box 347)
        - Correspondence, 1891-1910; 2 folders (Box 348, Folder 1-2)
        - Receipts and Miscellaneous, 1889-1904; 3 folders (Box 348, Folder 3-5)
      - Davis, Fanny L. (Mrs. John Lee Davis): Soldier's Additional - Homestead Right, 1900; 1 folder (Box 349, Folder 1)
      - DeLeon, Agnes and Maria: Congressional Petition, 1887-1890; 1 folder (Box 349, Folder 2)
      - District of Columbia: regarding tuberculin test for milk herds, 1906-1912; 1 folder (Box 349, Folder 3)
      - Edmond, Sarah H.: estate, 1887-1890; 1 folder (Box 349, Folder 4)
      - Flint, Laura A. (Mrs. Flint's School), 1900-1914; 1 folder (Box 349, Folder 5)
      - Ford, Milton: will, 1893-1894; 1 folder (Box 349, Folder 6)
      - Freeman, Edward C.: will, 1900-1911; 1 folder (Box 350, Folder 1)
      - Freeman, Isabel C.: will, 1905-1915; 1 folder (Box 350, Folder 2)
      - French Spoliation Claims, 1888-1896; 1 folder (Box 350, Folder 3)
      - Gauges, Philip: estate, 1903-1905; 1 folder (Box 350, Folder 4)
      - Greer, Robert, Jr.: will, 1893-1905; 1 folder (Box 350, Folder 5)
      - Hamilton v. Cutts, 1887-1892; 3 folders
        - Documents, 1887-1891; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, 1887-1892; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous Material, Printed Matter, 1887; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 3)
      - Havemeyer, Theodore A, 1897-1918; 2 folders
        - Estate Documents, 1897-1903; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 4)
        - Estate Correspondence, 1897-1918; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 5)
      - Hilton, Dorothy W.: will, 1898-1900; 1 folder (Box 351, Folder 6)
      - Holcombe, E. Prosser: regarding debts, 1905-1911; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 1)
      - Holt, Joseph (1807-1894) regarding will, 1857-1907; 8 folders
        - Documents, 1873-1904; 3 folders (Box 352, Folder 2-4)
        - Correspondence to & by Holt, Including Family, 1857-1890; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1895-1907; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous Material, undated; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 7)
        - Printed Matter, 1895-1898; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 8)
        - Receipts, etc., 1872-1897; 1 folder (Box 352, Folder 9)
      - Howell, Mary Stockton: estate, 1893-1900; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 1)
      - Hull v. Starkweather, 1889-1893; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 2)
      - Janin, Violet Blair (1848-1933): estate, 1929-1935; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 3)
      - Johnson v. Glass, 1906-1907; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 4)
      - Jones, Mary ("Minnie") E.: defendant, 1885-1899; 1 folder (Box 353, Folder 5)
      - King, Theodore I. regarding inquest, 1906-1907; 7 folders (Box 354, Folder 1-7)
      - Lamkins v. Carter, et al., 1896-1897; 1 folder (Box 354, Folder 8)
      - Lee, Anne Clymer Brooke: estate, 1904-1913; 1 box (Box 355)
      - Lester, Morgan regarding estate, 1889-1914; 1 box
        - documents, 1889-1902; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 1)
        - correspondence, 1897-1914; 3 folders
          - Mary E. Williams to Blair Lee, 1897-1914; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 2)
          - Mary E. Williams to Philip Gauges, 1897-1903; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 3)
          - miscellaneous, 1897-1909; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 4)
        - financial matters, 1889-1904; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 5)
        - miscellaneous materials, 1896-1901; 1 folder (Box 356, Folder 6)
      - Lusby, Francis W. regarding estate, 1878-1914; 4 boxes
        - documents, 1878-1912; 2 folders (Box 357, Folder 1-2)
        - correspondence by Earle Lusby, 1905-1914; 2 folders
          - correspondence by Earle Lusby, 1905-1908 May; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 3)
          - correspondence by Earle Lusby, 1908 May-1914; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 4)
        - correspondence by Frank J. Lusby, 1905-1912; 3 folders
          - correspondence by Frank J. Lusby, 1905-1907; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 5)
          - correspondence by Frank J. Lusby, 1908-1909; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 6)
          - correspondence by Frank J. Lusby, 1910-1912; 1 folder (Box 357, Folder 7)
        - correspondence by F. W. L., 1887-1895; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 1)
        - correspondence: miscellaneous, 1887-1912; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 2)
        - correspondence: Randolph-Macon Academy, 1905-1909; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 3)
        - correspondence by Mrs. Edward Shacklette, 1905 August-1907 June; 2 folders
          - correspondence by Mrs. Edward Shacklette, 1905 August-1906 August; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 4)
          - correspondence by Mrs. Edward Shacklette, 1906 September-1907 June; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 5)
        - correspondence: Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1906-1911; 1 folder (Box 358, Folder 6)
        - financial information, 1905-1913; 2 folders (Box 358, Folder 7-8)
        - Receipts, 1897-1913; 1 box (Box 359)
        - Checkbooks, 1904-1912; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 1)
        - Canceled Checks, 1900-1912; 2 folders (Box 360, Folder 2-3)
        - Canceled Checks Ledger, 1889-1912; 1 folder (Box 360, Folder 4)
      - Mangum v. Wise, 1892-1907; 1 box
        - correspondence, 1892-1906; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 1)
        - documents, 1892-1907; 2 folders (Box 361, Folder 2-3)
        - miscellaneous material, 1892-1907; 1 folder (Box 361, Folder 4)
      - Maryland and District of Columbia Regarding Roads, 1893-1921; 1 box (Box 362)
        Includes maps.
      - Mercer and Cary v. Brooke et al., 1880-1892; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 1)
      - McGuire and McGuire: legal separation, 1899; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 2)
      - McKim, Anne M. Clymer and Randolph, Rev.: real estate, 1899-1900; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 3)
      - McLachlen and White v. Garrett, 1878-1891; 1 folder (Box 363, Folder 4)
      - McLane, Allan (Anne M. Cropper) regarding estate, 1888-1912; 4 boxes
        - Documents, 1892-1896; 1 box (Box 364)
        - Correspondence, 1889-1912; 3 folders
          - Correspondence, 1892-1896; 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, 1896-1912; 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 2)
          - Miscellaneous, 1889-1907; 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence (John Cropper), 1888-1904; 2 boxes 4 folders
          - Correspondence (John Cropper), 1892-1894; 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence (John Cropper), 1895-1901; 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 5)
          - Miscellaneous Material, 1888-1904; 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 6)
            Includes financial documents.
          - Miscellaneous Material and Printed Matter, 1892-1893; 1 folder (Box 365, Folder 7)
          - Printed Matter, 1892; 1 box (Box 366)
          - Printed Matter, 1895; 1 box (Box 367)
      - McLane v. Bentley, 1886-1888; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 1)
      - Middleton v. Early, 1901; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 2)
      - Milhan v. Gibson, 1890-1893; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 3)
      - Minor, Rebecca: estate, 1900-1912; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 4)
      - Mulcahey v. Burke, 1891; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 5)
      - Nicholson v. Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co., 1907-1908; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 6)
      - O'Brien v. Brightwood Railway Co., 1899-1903; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 7)
      - Ohio Roofing Tile Co. v. Glen Burnie Clay Co., 1894-1898; 1 folder (Box 368, Folder 8)
      - Page, Florence L.: will, 1892-1899; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 1)
      - Palmer, Innis N. (1824-1900): estate, 1886-1900; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 2)
      - Perkins, Benjamin: claim against Russian government, 1871; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 3)
      - Perkins, Minerva M. v. Baltimore & Ohio Railroad Co., 1906-1907; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 4)
      - Ross and Sanford v. A Steam Dredge, 1884-1885; 1 folder (Box 369, Folder 5)
      - Scheley v. County Commissioners of Montgomery County, 1892-1910; 6 folders
        - Documents, 1905-1907; 2 folders (Box 369, Folder 6-7)
        - Correspondence, 1892-1910; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous Material, 1906-1907; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 2)
        - Printed Matter, 1907-1908; 2 folders (Box 370, Folder 3-4)
      - Shoemaker v. Curran, 1890-1902; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 5)
      - Siggers v. Snow, 1900-1901; 1 folder (Box 370, Folder 6)
      - Smith, Agnes regarding will, 1884-1901; 3 folders
        - Documents, 1889-1901; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence: Margaret Mack, Georgie M. Mack, 1887-1896; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, Mainly Financial, 1884-1895; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 3)
      - Sypher v. Foley, 1893-1899; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 4)
      - Thackeray v. Thackeray, 1885; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 5)
      - Thornton, Caroline Jones: trust fund, 1900-1913; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 6)
      - United States of America v. Glenn W. Cooper et al., undated; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 1)
      - United States Quartermaster General's Office: Miscellaneous Claims, 1882-1884; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 2)
      - United States Quartermaster General's Office: Miscellaneous Claims, 1880-1885; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 3)
      - United States Senate: Bill no. 2452 (Condemnation of Blair & Lee Families' Property), 1899-1904; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 4)
      - Waggaman, Thomas E. Bankruptcy: Correspondence, 1904-1920; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 5)
      - Waggaman, Thomas E. Bankruptcy: Miscellaneous Financial Material, 1892-1905; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 6)
      - Waters v. Greer, 1905; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 7)
      - Webb, Andrew B.: real estate, 1893; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 8)
      - Wilbur-Smith, Frances A, 1899-1920; 5 folders
        - estate correspondence by F. W.-S. to B. L, 1899-1920; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 1)
        - estate correspondence by others to B. L, 1901-1918; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, undated; 2 folders (Box 373, Folder 3-4)
        - Documents, Miscellaneous Material, Printed Matter, 1899-1915; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 5)
      - Wise, Mattie Davis v. Ross W. Wise, 1896-1900; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 6)
      - Wise, Thomas W. regarding estate, 1891-1904; 1 box 2 folders
        - documents, 1891-1902; 3 folders (Box 374, Folder 1-3)
        - correspondence, 1891-1904; 3 folders (Box 374, Folder 4-6)
        - financial material, 1892-1897; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 1)
        - miscellaneous material, 1896-1901; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 2)
      - Young v. Cushing, 1898-1899; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1877-1925; 2 boxes 4 folders
      Contains a random gathering of notes, letters, documents, and printed matter for miscellaneous cases.
      - A (general), 1896-1900; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 1)
      - B (general), 1879-1914; 2 folders (Box 376, Folder 2-3)
      - C (general), 1889-1909; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 4)
      - D (general), 1886-1912; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 5)
      - E (general), 1877-1887; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 6)
      - F (general), 1890-1892; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 7)
      - G (general), 1891-1911; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 8)
      - H (general), 1888-1925; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 1)
      - I - J (general), 1890-1907; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 2)
      - K (general), 1884-1891; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 3)
      - L (general), 1898-1918; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 4)
      - M (general), 1889-1918; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 5)
      - N - Q (general), 1889; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 6)
      - R (general), 1884-1913; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 7)
      - S (general), 1887-1899; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 1)
      - T (general), 1895-1912; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 2)
      - U - V (general), 1882-1912; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 3)
      - W - Z (general), 1891-1913; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - Notes, 1830-1918; 1 box (1 partial) 3 folders
      Contains legal notes in Blair Lee's hand as well as many in shorthand.
      - Legal notes, 1858-1918; 2 folders (Box 378, Folder 5-6)
      - Legal notes: shorthand, undated; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 7)
      - Records of St. Mary's County (Maryland) Court, 1830-1832; 1 box (partial) (Box 454)
  - Documents and Financial Material, 1857-1926; 25 boxes
    Consists of receipts, checkbooks, ledgers, account books, cancelled checks, insurance policies, and other documents of Blair Lee.
    - Receipts, 1888-1920; 14 boxes (Box 379, Box 380, Box 381)
    - Checkbooks, 1886-1923; 3 boxes (Box 393, Box 394, Box 395)
    - Ledgers, 1886-1920; 2 boxes (Box 396, Box 397)
    - Account Books, 1857-1919; 1 box (partial) (Box 397)
    - Canceled Checks, 1887-1925; 5 boxes (Box 398, Box 399, Box 400)
    - Insurance Policies, 1877-1926; 8 folders
      - Aetna, 1900-1905; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 1)
      - Arlington Fire Insurance Co., 1894-1906; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 2)
      - Georgia Home Insurance, 1897-1900; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 3)
      - Hartford Fire Insurance, 1910-1921; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 4)
      - Liverpool, London & Globe, 1896-1916; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Insurance Companies, 1877-1923; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 6)
      - Royal Insurance Co., Ltd., 1909-1912; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 7)
      - Security Insurance Co., 1923-1926; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 8)
    - Other Documents, 1887-1912; 1 folder (Box 403, Folder 9)
      Contains miscellaneous stock and bank certificates, as well as documents acknowledging membership in various organizations, and a diploma admitting Lee to practice in the U.S. Court of Claims.
  - Organizational Files, 1886-1923; 6 boxes
    Consists of files related to the Bar Association of the District of Columbia, Society of the Cincinnati in the State of Virginia, National Mary Washington Memorial Association, Metropolitan Club, Washington City Orphan Asylum, and Democratic National Publishing Company.
    Arranged by subject of file.
    - Bar Association of the District of Columbia, 1888-1909; 2 folders (Box 404, Folder 1-2)
      Contains letters and cards announcing meetings and dinners.
    - Metropolitan Club, 1890-1920; 2 folders (Box 404, Folder 3-4)
      Contains letters announcing meetings, advising on financial arrears, and replying to letters of recommendation for new members, and printed matter.
    - National Junior Republic, 1899-1905; 1 folder (Box 404, Folder 5)
      Contains letters and miscellaneous material concerning the situations of the young men and announcements of meetings.
    - Society of the Cincinnati in the State of Virginia, 1893-1918; 6 folders
      Contains correspondence, documents, miscellaneous material, and printed matter, much of it pertaining to Lee's expulsion and reinstatement in the organization.
      - Correspondence, 1893-1908; 4 folders
        - P. H. C. Cabell, 1896-1906; 1 folder (Box 404, Folder 6)
        - John Cropper, 1893-1906; 1 folder (Box 404, Folder 7)
        - George Ben Johnson, 1904-1908; 1 folder (Box 404, Folder 8)
        - Heth Lorton, 1901-1908; 1 folder (Box 404, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1895-1918; 1 folder (Box 404, Folder 10)
      - Documents, miscellaneous material, printed matter, 1899-1907; 1 folder (Box 404, Folder 11)
    - National Mary Washington Memorial Association, 1890-1923; 3 boxes
      Contains correspondence, photographs, account books, checks and checkbooks, documents, insurance policies, financial records, receipts, miscellaneous material, and printed matter for the organization of which Lee was the treasurer.
      - Correspondence, 1891-1923; 2 boxes
        - Frances Bernard Goolrick, 1898-1923; 1 box (Box 405)
        - E. T. Bushnell, 1905; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 1)
        - J. E. Caldwell & Co., 1891-1902; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 2)
        - Appleton P. Clark, Jr., 1898-1900; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 3)
        - Joseph K. Davison, 1900-1905; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 4)
        - Mary Desha, 1899-1910; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 5)
        - General, 1895-1914; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 6)
        - Margaret Hetzel, 1895-1899; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 7)
        - Susan R. Hetzel, 1897-1907; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 8)
        - Eleanor (Nelly) W. Howard, 1897-1919; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 9)
        - Minnie F. Mickley, 1911-1921; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 10)
        - Mary F. Waite, 1893-1902; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 11)
        - E. S. Wilcox, 1900; 1 folder (Box 406, Folder 12)
      - Account books, 1896-1903; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 1)
      - Checks and checkbooks, 1905-1912; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 2)
      - Documents and Insurance Policies, 1891-1908; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 3)
      - Financial Records, 1905-1921; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 4)
      - Financial Reports, 1902-1918; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous, 1898-1900; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 6)
      - Photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 7)
      - Printed matter, 1890-1905; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 8)
      - Receipts, 1898-1919; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 9)
      - Reports, 1896-1904; 1 folder (Box 407, Folder 10)
    - Washington City Orphan Asylum, 1886-1923; 1 box
      Contains correspondence, documents, financial matters, minutes of trustees' meetings, miscellaneous material, and printed matter for the organization of which Lee was the secretary.
      - Documents, 1891-1910; 1 folder (Box 408, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1888-1923; 7 folders
        - E. B. Beale, undated; 1 folder (Box 408, Folder 2)
        - J. J. Darlington, 1896-1919; 1 folder (Box 408, Folder 3)